# FLAVIEN CHAMAY

Hi, I'm a junior IT Python developer searching for new opportunities in France and beyond. I'm a Tech and Math enthusiast with a passion for A.I. and Backend development. I lived in Canada and in Europe, I have therefore experienced two different work worlds and have a certain flexibility towards that.



#### CONTACT

flavien.chamay@protonmail.com

**\** +33 06 80 44 71 60

Toulouse, France

My Personal Website

github.com/flavienChamay

in linkedin.com/in/flavienchamay/

### **IT SKILLS**

#### **Programming Languages**

**Python** 

C

Java

**OCaml** 

**SQL** 

LaTeX

**Operating Systems** 

Linux Manjaro | Ubuntu

Windows 10 | 7

Software & Tools

GitHub/Git

**Fmacs** 

**PyCharm** 

**Eclipse** 

Heroku/Linode



Django

**Blockchain** 

A.I.

Languages

English C2 grade

**Native French** 



# CERTIFICATES & RECOMMENDATIONS

**HackerRank Python Basic HackerRank Problem Solving Basic EFSET Standard English Test C2** Recommendation Letter from B&D

#### INTERESTS

A.I., Extraterrestrial life, Mathematical logic, Hacking.

# **PROJECTS**

- Web Blog (Django, Linode, Heroku, Personal project in progress).
- Simple Blockchain (Python, Personal project in progress): coding of the proof of work, the wallet and data encryption.
- Tic-Tac-Toe Game (Python, Personal project in progress): Minimax algorithm for computer player, CLI interface, save/load mechanisms.
- Planning by satisfiability of logical formulas (Touist, Academic project): coding, modeling and benchmarking of logic problem solving A.I..
- NeoCampus, real-time sensors (Java, Academic project): GUI coding and data re-
- Caesar encryption (C, Academic project): encryption/decryption of text files.
- Websites (Google site): Creation and maintenance for various clients.

# **WORK HISTORY**

**2017 - 2020** 

Auterive & Toulouse, France

math April 2011 - August 2011

Staples Quebec, Canada

February 2008 - June 2010

Becton, Dickinson and Company Quebec, Canada

**Tutor for private lessons** in Maths and C.S.

Computer Repairman & **IT Consultant** 

**Packaging Operator** 

#### EDUCATION

**2017 - 2020** 

Paul Sabatier University **Toulouse France** 

2011 - 2016

Paul Sabatier University Toulouse, France

**♀** CEGEP François-Xavier-Garneau Quebec, Canada

C.S. Bachelor Degree

1st & 2nd cycle in Physics 2<sup>nd</sup> cycle in Maths

High School Diploma in S.T.E.M.

#### **GENERAL SKILLS**

Implement/integrate an app to a system Analyse origin of a malfunction Create a model/specification of an app Identify/protect confidential data Maintain/develop an app Optimise space/time complexity of an algo. Assess client's need Understand/write doc. in Eng/Fr

#### **HOBBIES & OCCUPATIONS**

